unitedcats.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy / Unitedcats

Welcome to United Dogs and United Cats, an online dog and cat lovers community, operated by United Pets Ltd (registered in Europe, Estonia). 

We are happy that you are here and want to let you know that **we care deeply about your privacy and security, we make sure you have nothing to worry about!**

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use your personal identifying information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. By using United Dogs and United Cats, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in the Privacy Policy. 

**Information we collect**

When you register to become a member of United Dogs and United Cats, we collect your name and e-mail address. To complete your profile we additionally collect your birthday, gender, country and optionally state. When you register your dog and/or cat we collect name of your dog / cat, optionally nicknames, kennel name, dog / cat breed, gender and birthday.

When you enter United Dogs and United Cats, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all United Dogs and United Cats visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users' computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser, unless you choose to remember your session with our site. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to United Dogs and United Cats. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use United Dogs and United Cats, you may set up your personal profile for yourself and your dog(s) and cat(s), form relationships, send messages, perform searches, form clubs, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your animals’ buddies list.

When you invite your friends to see your dog or cat profiles or send messages through United Dogs and United Cats, we collect and maintain information associated with those messages, including e-mail addresses and content.

**Controlling your personal information**

You post your and your pets personal information on United Dogs and United Cats at your own risk. Under profile settings you can limit access to your personal information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We can’t control the actions of other users or visitors with whom you may choose to share your and your pets pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that user and pets’ information you post on United Dogs or United Cats will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. United Dogs and United Cats is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the United Dogs and United Cats. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of user and pet information may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users or visitors have copied or stored your user or pet information.

Access and control over user personal and pets’ information on United Dogs and United Cats is readily available under profile settings. United Dogs and Untied Cats users may modify or delete any of their profile information and their pets profiles information at any time by logging into their account. Individuals who wish to deactivate their United Dogs and United Cats account or their pets profiles may do so by sending a request to services@uniteddogs.com. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members or visitors of United Dogs and United Cats.

United Dogs and United Cats takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because e-mail and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services.

**Age restriction**

United Dogs and United Cats are not intended for persons under the age of 13. We do not knowingly market to, or solicit information, accept service or collect information from any person under the age of 13. If United Dogs and United Cats becomes aware that any person submitting information to our site is under the age of 13, we will attempt to delete the account and any related information as soon as possible. We require that only persons 13 years of age or older use the Site. By registering to United Dogs and United Cats, you hereby represent that you are at least 13 years old.

**Updating Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices. Upon posting changes we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check this Privacy Policy from time to time to inform yourself of any changes.

If you have any questions about the security of United Dogs or United Cats websites, please feel free to contact us.

Date of Last Revision: June 3th 2014
